# Luqman Ali

# Full stack Developer (PHP, Laravel)

Haripur 22820 luqmanalihrp@gmail.com +92 330 5612123

Full Stack Developer with more than two years of experience building performant and scaleable web applications and microservices. I have worked with LAMP tech stack (PHP & Laravel).

I'm fluent in English, Urdu & Punjabi and have excellent communication skills.

# Education

# **Graduate in Software Engineering (BSSE)**

International Islamic University Islamabad - Islamabad September 2019 to Present

#### Skills

- Laravel (1 year)
- RESTful API development (6 months)
- PHP 8+ (1 year)
- SQL databases (2 years)
- CSS [SCSS & Bootstrap] (3 years)

# **Work Experience**

### Junior PHP Developer

Zinlab Technologies - Islamabad Aug 2020 to June 2022

# Assistant Store Manager

Medbazar - Islamabad May 2020 to Aug 2022

# **Projects**

# Repo

Repo is a custom-built CMS built in Laravel 8. Made on demand for major sites with performance and scalability in mind.

I was responsible for developing the CMS and creating RESTful APIs to fetch content from the database for the front-end views.

#### • Learn IT

A rival startup of Educative Inc, required a distance learning management system with video feeds, text & images.

I was responsible for the development, testing, deployment, and maintenance of the Project.

# Merijaga

A complex network of spacing & warehousing renting solutions with an integrated inventory management system.

I was responsible for the development & communication with clients.

# MedBazar

MedBazar is an E-commerce store for Medicine. I was involved in its development via Shopify, design, testing, SEO & Marketing.

MedBazar was an early-stage startup.